globus-inter.com 2017-05-17

# Privacy policy

_description_ Privacy policy 

The “GLOBUS INTERCOM” Ltd (hereinafter referred to as Company) responsibly approaches your privacy. You will learn on this page about our privacy policy and how we treat the collected and received personal information.

To increase the quality of service and personal information security, the Company reserves the right to change the privacy policy on its own.

Personal information collection

Personal information may become available for the Company in many ways, like web-site cookies, during registration for the software of the Company, by processing of your answers to polls or contents you view.

During registration on the Company’s site and using the client application, the Company requests your personal information that may include full name, email, date of birth, sex, postcode, area of interest, tax information and other information to ensure better services and compliance with national laws. The Company may collect information about clients’ web activity with log files of its server.

Apart of that, Company may get your personal information during holidays, advertising campaigns, and real-time polls, held by the Company and its Partners, and other events.

How we use your personal information

The main purpose of the personal information by the Company is to ensure better services for its clients and content Users.

To get closer to the content Users and to realize their interests, Company processes and studies personal information obtained from different sources.

Personal information protection

The Company **does not sell, distribute or lease your personal information** to the third persons or companies except cases provided by law directly.

Use of cookies technology

To improve our site we use the “cookies” technology to make your visits more comfortable. “Cookies” is small records by web-server in your web-browser. That enables your browser to save information that can be requested by our web-server in the future.

"Cookies" are generally used:

  * for User identification;
  * for visits calculation. Each client browser receives unique record that is used to identify the site visitors.

Notifications of changes

Company reserves the right to supplement or amend its privacy policy at any time. In case of serious changes the Company will inform you by sending notifications to your email saved in the client database or by placing of easy to see notification on its web-site.

GLOBUS INTERCOM Ltd
